https://www.plascore.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, title, company, address, phone number, email address, and other relevant data. Questions or comments submitted by visitors may also include personal information. We do not require personal information to obtain access to most of our site. We do, however, require it to download product information, order products and take advantage of certain other features of our site.
We use the information that visitors provide for such purposes as processing and responding to requests, improving our operations, and communicating with visitors about our products, services and businesses. Subsidiaries and external service providers participate in some of these activities, but we do not sell or rent personal information to unrelated businesses for direct marketing purposes. Also, as our business evolves we may transfer or acquire businesses and related assets, and we may transfer information about customers and site visitors in connection with such transactions.
Our web server also automatically collects non-personally-identifiable information such as the domain name of the site providing the visitor with Internet access, but not the visitor’s user name. Other examples of information collected by our server include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect the visitor’s computer to the Internet, the visitor’s browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics. We use this information in the aggregate to measure the use of our site and to administer and improve our site.
We also use cookies to distinguish repeat visitors from first time visitors and provide visitors a personalized experience on our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to the hard drive of a visitor’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to allow visitors to use the site without logging on upon returning, to auto-populate email forms, to make improvements and to better tailor our site to our visitors’ needs.
To the extent required or permitted by law, we may also collect, use and disclose personal information in connection with security related or law enforcement investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities or complying with legal requirements.
We take commercially reasonable precautions to keep all information obtained from our online visitors secure against unauthorized access and use and we periodically review our security measures.
Our site contains links to other web sites. These sites are not covered by this privacy statement, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other sites.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site.
© 2008-2020 Plascore, Inc.
click to view full site
